https://objentis.com/en/data-protection-policy/

Data Protection Policy
Last Updated: 29.05.2018
The protection of your personal data is very important to us. Therefore we process your data exclusively on the basis of legal regulations. In this privacy policy we inform you about the most important aspects of how we process personal data on our website.
Contacting us
If you contact us by e-mail, your details will be stored for six months to process the request and in case of follow-up questions. We will not share this information without your consent.
Data Categories
As a general rule, we process only the personal data that we receive from you in the course of our business relationship. Your personal data includes your name, address, contact details, date and place of birth, nationality, etc., as well as credentials (for example, identity card data) and authentication data (for example, a signature sample). In addition, this includes order data (for example, payment orders), data from the fulfillment of our contractual obligations (for example, sales data in payment transactions), advertising and sales data, documentation data, register data, information from your electronic communication with OBJENTIS (cookies, etc.) and data to meet legal and regulatory requirements.
Purposes of processing data
We process your personal data in accordance with data protection regulations for the following purposes:
To fulfill contractual obligations (Article 6 (1) (b) GDPR)
The processing of personal data (Article 4 (2) GDPR) is for the purpose of providing and brokering our services. The specific details for the purpose of data processing can be found in the respective contract documents and terms and conditions.
As per your consent (Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR)
If you have given us consent to process your personal data, processing will only take place in accordance with the purposes set out in the consent declaration and to the extent agreed therein. A given consent can be revoked at any time with effect for the future. The revocation of consent does not affect the legality of the data processed until the revocation.
For the protection of legitimate interests (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR)
If necessary in the interests of OBJENTIS Software Integration GmbH or a third party, data processing beyond the actual performance of the contract may take place in order to safeguard our legitimate interests or those of such a third party. In the following cases, data processing takes place to safeguard legitimate interests:
Measures for business management and further development of services and products
Measures to protect employees and customers and property of OBJENTIS Software Integration GmbH
If required due to legal action
Data recipients
Within OBJENTIS Software Integration GmbH, your data will only be received by those employees who need it to fulfill contractual, statutory and regulatory obligations or a legitimate interest.
Storage duration
We process your personal data, to the extent necessary, for the duration of the entire business relationship (from initiation and execution of a contract until termination) and in accordance with statutory civil law retention and documentation requirements, for example those stemming from the Austrian Commercial Code (UGB).
Cookies
Our website uses so-called “cookies.” These are small text files that are stored on your device by your browser. They do no harm to your device.
We use cookies to make our offers more user-friendly. Some cookies remain stored on your device until you delete them, as this allows us to recognize your browser on your next visit.
If you object to the use of cookies, you can set your browser to inform you when cookies are placed and only allow them in individual cases.
Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of our website.
Web analytics
To enable the statistical evaluation of traffic on our website, we use the program AWStats. This program, available from the website http://www.awstats.org/, is a freely available web analytics software distributed under the GNU General Public License. It is used to evaluate log files that our web server generates based on visitor requests. No cookies are used, as the statistical analysis is performed via the log files. These log files contain IP addresses, which are usually not assignable to specific persons. The data used for analysis is not consolidated with other data sources and is furthermore deleted after the statistical evaluation – within six months at the latest. Unlike with other analysis programs, data is not transmitted to any third parties.
External links
To keep you optimally informed, we provide external links on our website that take you to third-party websites. Unless obvious, we indicate whenever a link is external. OBJENTIS Software Integration GmbH has no influence on the content and design of externally linked pages operated by third parties. This also means that the information in this privacy policy does not apply on such pages.
Data security
OBJENTIS Software Integration GmbH uses technical and organizational security measures to protect your data against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction or access by unauthorized persons. Our security measures are constantly being improved and adapted in line with technological developments.
Your rights
As a general rule, you are granted the right of access, rectification, deletion (“erasure”), restriction, data portability, revocation and opposition. If you believe that the processing of your data violates data protection laws or that your data protection rights have otherwise been violated in some way, you may file a complaint with the supervisory authority. In Austria, this is the data protection authority.
Österreichische Datenschutzbehörde
Wickenburggasse 8
1080 Wien
Telephone: +43 1 52 152-0
Email: dsb@dsb.gv.at
How to contact us
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy in particular or regarding privacy at OBJENTIS in general, please contact us:
OBJENTIS Software Integration GmbH
Mariahilfer Strasse 3, 1060 Vienna
FN181484p
Data protection officer: Wolfgang Karas
Telephone: +43 1 58 568 00 – 600
Email: datenschutz@objentis.com
Modification of this Privacy Policy
For legal and/or organizational reasons, changes or adjustments to our privacy policy will be required from time to time. Please take note of the latest version of our privacy policy.
SPLIT
SPLIT - Security Protocol Interaction Testing in Practise.
OBJENTIS as a partner in an international research project.
Read More
SAP-Testconsulting
In many companies, SAP solutions represent the backbone of IT systems, for they are often used to control critical business processes. As a result, interface development and adaptations to meet the needs of customers involve significant complexity.
Read More
Mobile Application Test
The advance and proliferation of applications for mobile end devices has taken on a new dynamic in recent years. The countless different devices, not to mention the diversity of platforms and operating systems, presents new challenges to quality assurance teams in particular. Usability is a critical success factor, but security, optimal interoperability of hardware and software, and performance are also keys to success.
Read More
